(Leonard:)You know the best part
of working in the clean room?
(Leonard:)No allergies.
(Leonard:)Check it out.
(inhales deeply)
Oh, that-that...
that's a lot of oxygen.
(chuckles)
(Howard:)We should get
going to Amy's.
(Leonard:)Can you believe
there was a time
(Leonard:)when we would have
needed an array
(Leonard:)of giant Cherenkov telescopes
to detect cosmic particles?
(Leonard:)And here we are building
our own multi-wire detector
(Leonard:)like a couple of badasses.
(Howard:)I know. If we were still single,
(Howard:)we'd be tripping
over all that booty.
(Leonard:)Ladies do love a man dressed
like a kitchen garbage bag.
(Leonard:)Oh, no.
(Howard:)How the hell
did a pigeon get in here?
(Leonard:)You shut the loading
doors, right?
I thought you did.
(Leonard:)Do you know what a
disaster this is?!
(Howard:)You mean 'cause this room isn't
supposed to have dust in it,
(Howard:)and we just let in
a flying crap machine?!